englishleap.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy

##  Privacy Policy

Leap Learning Solutions (“EnglishLeap.com”) takes your privacy seriously. EnglishLeap.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy, and this privacy policy explains our data collection, use, and disclosure practices. This policy covers how EnglishLeap.com treats personal information that EnglishLeap.com collects and receives from you.

EnglishLeap.com provides its service (the “Service”) to you subject to the [Terms of Service](http://www.englishleap.com/terms-of-service)  and the following Privacy Policy ("PP"), which may be updated by us from time to time without notice to you.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

When you register, EnglishLeap.com collects personal information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, spoken and studied languages and any other personal or preference information that you freely enter, as well as your profile picture.

EnglishLeap.com will use your personal information for the following general purposes: (i) to provide you with Services; (ii) to respond to your questions and comments; (iii) to communicate with you via regular mail and email (or other electronic means) about Services; for (iv) statistical purposes and (v) otherwise as described to you at the point of collection.

When you use the Service, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, enrol in events and courses, and transmit information through various channels. EnglishLeap.com stores and collects this information so that EnglishLeap.com can provide you with the Service and offer personalized features.

EnglishLeap.com does not monitor the information you include in your Profile, but EnglishLeap.com shall have the right (but not the obligation) in it sole discretion to cancel your Profile, if it violates the TOS, the rights of third parties or it is otherwise objectionable. EnglishLeap.com receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, EnglishLeap.com cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. EnglishLeap.com uses information for customizing the advertising and content you see, fulfil your requests for products and services, improve our Services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal purpose and external clients.

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to use some features of the Service of EnglishLeap.com that require you to "sign in".

EnglishLeap.com lets other entities that show advertisements or provide services on some of our web pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, and not this policy. Advertisers or other entities do not have access to EnglishLeap.com's cookies.

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We display your Profile information (except your email address and password) to people browsing for friends, and to support other Site functions. EnglishLeap.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with third parties except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

EnglishLeap.com responds to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

EnglishLeap.com believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of EnglishLeap.com's TOS, or as otherwise required by law.

EnglishLeap.com transfers information about you if EnglishLeap.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, EnglishLeap.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information can be collected and used by others. By posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

EnglishLeap.com limits the access to personal information about you to employees who EnglishLeap.com believes to have reasonable need to come into contact with that information, to provide products or the Service to you or in order to do their jobs.

EnglishLeap.com has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with regulations to protect personal information about you. However, data transmissions over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, EnglishLeap.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to EnglishLeap.com.

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Web sites to which this Site links do not operate under this Privacy Policy. EnglishLeap.com recommends that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other web sites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.

**CONTACTING ENGLISHLEAP.COM**

You may obtain a copy of the personal information about you that you provide through the Site or otherwise request that EnglishLeap.com updates, makes changes or deletes personal information by sending an email to contact[-a-t-]EnglishLeap.com.
